var data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who were Harry's parents?",
    a: "Henry and Maggie Potter",
    b: "William and Elizabeth Potter",
    c: "James and Lily Potter",
    d: "Voldemort",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In order of birth, who are the seven Weasley siblings?",
    a: "Percy, Bill, George, Charlie, Fred, Ron, Ginny",
    b: "George, Fred, Percy, Bill, Charlie, Ron, Ginny",
    c: "Bill, Charlie, Percy, Fred, George, Ron, Ginny",
    d: "Charlie, Bill, Percy, Fred, George, Ron, Ginny",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What are the three Unforgivable Curses?",
    a: "Impedimenta, Incarcerous and Incendio",
    b: "Avada Kedavra, Crucio and Imperio",
    c: "Expelliarmus, Expecto Patronum and Diffindo",
    d: "Rictusempra, Crucio and Flipendo",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which of these Hogwarts professors teaches Transfiguration?",
    a: "Snape",
    b: "Sprout",
    c: "McGonagall",
    d: "Voldemort",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "At the end of Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone, which professor removes his turban to reveal Voldemort on the back of his head?",
    a: "Quirrel",
    b: "Snape",
    c: "Lockhart",
    d: "Hagrid",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Who first shows Harry the diary of Tom Riddle?",
    a: "Moaning Myrtle",
    b: "Nearly Headless Nick",
    c: "Ethernet",
    d: "Fawkes",
    answer: 1
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Who was Tom Marvolo Riddle?",
    a: "Harry's Father",
    b: "Harry's Mother",
    c: "Sirius Black",
    d: "Voldemort",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What's the only book in the Harry Potter series that doesn't feature Lord Voldemort?",
    a: "The Sorcerer's Stone",
    b: "The Prisoner of Azkaban",
    c: "The Deathly Hallows",
    d: "IDK",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Who was the Prisoner of Azkaban, and was he guilty of the crime he was accused of committing?",
    a: "James Potter and not guilty",
    b: "Cornelius Fudge and guilty",
    c: "Sirius Black and not guilty",
    d: "Rubeus Hagrid and guilty",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Who is the Half-Blood Prince?",
    a: "Voldemort",
    b: "Dumbledore",
    c: "Severus Snape",
    d: "Owl of Harry",
    answer: 3
  }
];